onlinepictureproof.com 2017-06-06

# Online Picture Proof | Online picture Proofing and sales service for photographers | Proof photos online

This privacy policy sets out how “Online Picture Proof” uses and protects any information that you give “Online Picture Proof” when you use this website.

“Online Picture Proof” is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. **We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to any third party.**

Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

**What we collect**

We may collect the following information:

  * your name & business name
  * contact information including email address
  * demographic information such as post code, preferences and interests
  * other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers

**What we do with the information we gather**

 ****We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service.

**Please note:**

  * We may use the information to improve our products and services.
  * We may periodically send promotional email about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail.
  * We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.
  * “Your Credit or Debit Card numbers are transmitted directly to the banking network [Paypal] for authorization. We do not know/record the card number anywhere.”

**Links to other websites**

 ****Our website may contain links to enable you to visit other websites of interest easily. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question. **  
**

******Controlling your personal information******

 ****We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. You can check the information that we hold about you by emailing us. If you find any inaccuracies we will delete or correct it promptly. ****

 **How we use cookies**

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to your needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system. Overall, cookies enable us to provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

“Online Picture Proof” may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.
